you there's this scene
from Carl Sagan's Contact
the movie version of
it where you they
kind of alien life
and it's this international
panel that's like you
know people to be
humanities representative to meet
the
And one of the
questions they asked one
of the is you
if you could ask
the any one question
what would it be
And one of the
characters says I would
ask how did you
do it How did
you manage to get
through this technological adolescence
without destroying yourselves How
did you make it
through And ever since
I saw it it
like 20 years ago
I think I saw
that movie it's kind
of with me And
that's the frame that
I used which is
that you know we
are knocking on the
of these incredible capabilities
right The ability to
basically machines out of
right I think it
was inevitable that the
instant we started working
with fire
but how we handle
it is not inevitable
And so I think
the next few years
we're going to be
with you how do
we keep these systems
under control that are
highly autonomous and smarter
than any human How
do we make sure
that individuals don't
misuse them